Alright, so...
imagine this.
You're walking down the street, right? Minding your own  business, scrolling through your phone, probably watching some cat video or  a  guy flipping pancakes in slow motion.
And then-bam! Out of  nowhere-a pigeon lands in front of  you.
But this isn't just any  pigeon.
This pigeon is wearing a  tiny hat.
Now, you're thinking, "Okay, weird, but kind of  cute."
But as  you step closer, the pigeon stares you down.
Like, full-on eye contact.
And then-it speaks.
Yeah, the pigeon just straight-up says, "You're late."
Late for what? Who knows? But before you can ask,, it flies awayy.
So now you're chasing this pigeon down the street like a  maniac, yelling, "What am  I late for?!" People are  staring, someone's recording you-probably for TikTok-but you don't care because this hat-wearing, talking pigeon clearly knows something you don't.
You follow it all  the way to a  park, and  it lands on  this bench next to an  old  man feeding ducks.
You're out  of  breath, you're confused, and  you're still yelling, "What am  I late for?" And the old  man looks at  you and  says, "Finally.
You're here."
And that's when you wake up.
Turns out,, you've been dreaming this entire time.
Except...
when you look at  your nightstand, there's a  tiny pigeon hat just sitting there.
Beat.
Anyway, that's why I don't drink energy drinks afteer 10 PM.